<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Kinaetron</title>
    <link>/Blog/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Kinaetron</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 10:36:28 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/Blog/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Moonworks Resources</title>
      <link>/Blog/posts/moonworks-resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 10:36:28 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>/Blog/posts/moonworks-resources/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This article goes over all of the resources available for Moonworks at the time of writing. Please also keep in mind that Evan Hemsley the developer of Moonworks was also one of the main developers of SDL_GPU which the  Moonworks Graphics API pretty much maps to. So there will be a lot of cross over information between the two frameworks.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;moonworks-graphics-tests&#34;&gt;Moonworks Graphics Tests&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So the author of Moonworks Evan wrote up a nice little project showing new users how to do standard graphics programming operations in Moonworks, such as getting a clear window up, rendering a triangle, rendering a texture and a whole host of other graphics programming examples.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moonworks Setup</title>
      <link>/Blog/posts/moonworks-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 19:15:47 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>/Blog/posts/moonworks-setup/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;intro&#34;&gt;Intro&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve been tinkering around With the Moonworks Framework for last few months. I found this to be a great development framework and is pretty much perfect for the kind of games I want to develop. Saying all that though, I do find that the documentation for new people is pretty slim of the ground, so I thought it would be a good idea to write up something that would help other people on their journey to using it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intro Post</title>
      <link>/Blog/posts/intropost/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 10:36:28 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>/Blog/posts/intropost/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;So I&amp;rsquo;m Kinaetron. I&amp;rsquo;ve been developing games for an embarrsinginly long time and I&amp;rsquo;ve been ranting and raving about the total lack of written articles about game development for a good while now, so here I am actually writing stuff down.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For the time being I want to write about game development projects I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing with a game dev framework called Moonworks.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So what is Moonworks ? It&amp;rsquo;s a fairly low level game development framework that I&amp;rsquo;ve been playing around for the last few months you can read up the details about it &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/MoonsideGames/MoonWorks&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. I found out about while playing Samurai Gunn 2, a game developed by one of my favourite indie game developers Beau Blyth (Teknopants). Moonworks is being used to develop the new version of Samurai Gunn 2, the current one up on steam was made in Game Maker Studio.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
