<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Graphics Programming on Kinaetron</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313///Blog/tags/graphics-programming/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Graphics Programming on Kinaetron</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 14:37:10 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313///Blog/tags/graphics-programming/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Moonworks Graphics Intro</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313///Blog/posts/moonworks-graphics-intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 14:37:10 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313///Blog/posts/moonworks-graphics-intro/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;intro&#34;&gt;Intro&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now that the basics of setting up a Moonworks project is out of the way we can start jumping into the juicer stuff. In this article we&amp;rsquo;re going to render a triangle, this task is considered the graphics programming equivalent to the hello world. But before that I&amp;rsquo;m going to try and give enough context that you&amp;rsquo;ll have some understanding of what&amp;rsquo;s happening under the hood.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;How did graphics programmers land on rendering a triangle as the most basic operation? Triangles at this point are graphics programming standards for rendering. Most of the time when you see a more complex object in a 3D movie or video game it&amp;rsquo;s just thousands upon thousands of triangles put together to make that new object. So you&amp;rsquo;re probably wondering why triangles specifically though, why not a rectangle or a &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=thOifuHs6eY&#34;&gt;hexagon&lt;/a&gt; instead? Well, they are easy to work with as they only have 3 points in space, they can be used to make other primitive shapes easily too, which makes computation pretty fast and simple in comparison to other polygons that could have been used. It&amp;rsquo;s efficient too, modern GPUs (Graphics Processing Unit) are designed specifically to draw triangles quickly.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
